ILR School Dean's Office Additional Records /4028
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Dean's Office Additional Records
1943-1978
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
Moore, David G.
/4028
10 cubic feet
10 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3079851
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 02, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 21, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3006: ILR School Dean's Office Publications /3085: ILR School Dean's Office Files /4014: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4054: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4047: ILR School Fiscal Office Additional Records /4082: ILR School Dean's Office Records /4100: ILR School Dean's Office "Report of the ILR Review Panel" Background Documentation /4123: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Records /4144: ILR School Dean's Office Files Additional
Moore, David G.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Dean's Office; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Administration.
3079851
- FS-1 Professional Staff (General), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- FS- la SMIS, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- FS-2 Non- Professional (General), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- FS-3-1 Miscellaneous, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- FS-3-2 Salary Program, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- FS-4 Director of Budget (Cornell University), 1956-1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- FS-5 Controller (Cornell University), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- FS-6 Director of Finance, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- FS-6 Director of Finance and Correspondence from Business Office Related to Budget, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- FS-6a Assistant Director of Finance and Course Section Analysis, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- FS-7 Grants (General), 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- FS-7-2 General Electric, 1959-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- FS-7-5 Research Grants (Cost Sharing), 1966-1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- FS-8 NYS Division of Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- FS-9 Accessory Instruction, 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- FS-10-1 Frank W. Pierce Lectures to 1969-70 (Kaldor Lectures), 1953-1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- FS-10-1 Frank W. Pierce Lectures #1-3 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- FS-10-1 Frank W. Pierce Lectures, John R. Coleman, Spring, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Pierce Lectures, April 20-22, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Fs-10-1 Pierce Memorial Lecture Series, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Fs-10-1 Festschrift Dean McKersie's Foreword, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- FS-10-1 Pierce Memorial Lecture Series- Fall, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- FS-10-1 Pierce Memorial Lecture Series April 20-22, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- FS-10-1 Pierce Memorial Lecture Series May, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- FS-10-1 Publication of Pierce Memorial Lectures, 1970 Lectures, and Lectureship, 1964-1972 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- FS-10 Mary Donlon Lectures, 1956-1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- A-8 Dean's Reports, 1947-1952 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- A-8 Dean's Reports, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- A-8 Dean's Reports, 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Council of Presidents- Minutes, Reports, and Agendas, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Council of Presidents- Minutes, Reports, and Agendas, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Region II Council of Presidents and President's Conference, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Saul Wallen Fund for Minority Studies (Part 1), 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Saul Wallen Fund for Minority Studies (Part 2), 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Saul Wallen Fund for Minority Studies (Part 3), 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- FS-10-2 Saul Wallen Financial- Monthly Statements, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Saul Wallen Fund Contributions, 1969-1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Saul Wallen Fund Contributions, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Frank S. Columbus Memorial, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Recruiting 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Correspondences (Part 1), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Correspondences (Part 2), 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Correspondences (Part 3), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Correspondences (Part 4), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Correspondences (Part 5), 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Correspondences (Part 6), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Correspondences (Part 7), 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Recruiting Correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Candidates A- H (Part 1), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Candidates A- H (Part 2), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Candidates I- N, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Candidates O- Z, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Recruiting Misc., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Allen, Steven, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Atrostic, Barbara, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Benham, Harry, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Borjas, George (Part 1), 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Borjas, George (Part 2), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Devaney, Barbara, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Dooley, Martin, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Duguay, Gary, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Farber, Henry (Part 1), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Farber, Henry (Part 2), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Farber, Henry (Part 3), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Fogel, Walter, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Hoffmann, Saul, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Undergraduate Program Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Misc. Notes and Correspondences (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Undergraduate Curriculum Committee, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Undergraduate Curriculum Committee 67-70 (Part 1), 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Undergraduate Curriculum Committee 67-70 (Part 2), 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- G-2 State University of New York, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- G-2 State University of New York 71-72 (Part 1), 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- G-2 State University of New York 71-72 (Part 2), 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- G-2 State University of New York 74 (Part 1), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- G-2 State University of New York 74 (Part 2), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- G-2 State University of New York 75 (Part 1), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- G-2 State University of New York 75 (Part 2), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Gordon, Gerald- Annual Report, 1966-1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Foltman, Felician F., 1950-1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Francis, Ivor S., 1968-1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Frank. William W., 1965-1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Gagala, Kenneth L., 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Galenson, Walter (Social Science Research Council), 1966-1976 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Gray, Lois S., 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Gross, James A., 1966-1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Gruenfeld, Leopold Re: Job Satisfaction, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Gruenfeld, Leopold, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Gruenfeld, Leopold, 1962-1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Hildebrand, George, 1961-1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Jensen, Vernon, 1949-1976 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- P-1 Alberti, Giorgio, 1967-1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- P-1 Aldrich, Howard E., 1969-1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- P-1 Aronson, Robert L., 1950-1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- P-1 Blumen, Isadore, 1955-1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- P-1 Clark, M. Gardner- Annual Reports, 1950-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- P-1 Coghill, Mary Ann- Annual Reports, 1961-1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- P-1 Cullen, Donald E.- Annual Reports and Appointment, 1953-1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- P-1 Daniel, Cletus E., 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- P-1 DeCotiis, Thomas, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- P-1 Doherty, Robert E., 1962-1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- P-1 Donovan, Ronald, 1960-1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- P-1 Dyer, Lee D., 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- P-1 Ehrenberg, Ronald G., 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- P-1 Farley, Jennie: Annual Report and Appendix I-IIX, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- P-1 Farley, Jennie- Annual Reports and Appendix IX-IIXX, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- P-1 Farley, Jennie: Appendices, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Bethel, Terry, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Craver, Charles, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fleischli, George, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Gentile, Carolyn, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Krouner, Leonard, 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Hartog, Jack, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Procedure for Approval of New Programs (State Education Dept.), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- ASPA Long-Range Planning Committee, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- National Advisory Council on Minority Business Enterprise, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Hotz, Joseph, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Johnson, George, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Katz, Harry, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Kaufman, Bruce, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Lazear, Edward, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Lazear, Edward, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Lee, Robert, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Leigh, Duane, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Lucas, Robert, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Madden, Janice, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Medoff, James, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Mulvey, Charles, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Neumann, George, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Neumann, George, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Plotnick, Robert, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Polachek, Solomon, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Smith, Sharon, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Stromsdorfer, Ernst, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Svejnar, Jan, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Svejnar, Jan, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Watcher, Susan, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Wolpin, Kenneth, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Annual Reports, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- NYC Credit, Manpower Programs, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Reduction in Force, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Responsibility Center Analysis, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- War on Waste Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Moberly, Robert B., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Balfour, Alan, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Aboud, Antone, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Abrams, Roger, 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Nolan, Dennis, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Wolkinson, Ben, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Wheeler, Hoyt, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Wheeler, Hoyt (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Anderson, Arvid, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Ashenfelter, Orley, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Bernstein, Irving, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Bhatt, Bhal, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Blum, Albert A., 1966 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Eames, Patricia, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Edelstein, J. David, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Fishgold, Herbert, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Frank, Beryl, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Grunes, Willa, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Howells, Richard W. L., 1967 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Jones, Dallas, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Komives, John, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Kruger, Daniel, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Kuhn, James Wesley, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Busch, Karen S., 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Search Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Kilberg, W., 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- CB Search Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- International Search Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- O.B. Search Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Junior Search Labor Law, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Senior Search Labor Law, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- ILR Materials Vol. 1 Annual Report, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- ILR Materials Vol.II Special Extension Report, Miscellaneous Summaries, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Report on Four-Hour Advanced Electives, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- NYSSILR Labor Advisory Committee, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Advisory Council Meetings, 1952-1955 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Advisory Council Meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Advisory Council Meetings, 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Advisory Council Meetings, 1961-1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Organization of the School (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Ives, Irving: The Story of a Legislative Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- NYS Legislature- Bills for Establishing the School, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Poems, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Annual Faculty Meetings, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Annual Faculty Meetings, 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Annual Faculty Meetings, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Annual Faculty Meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Annual Faculty Meetings, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Annual Faculty Meetings, NYSSILR Summary and Report on Division of Extension and Public Services, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Annual Faculty Meetings, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Annual Faculty Meetings, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Organizational Behavior Dept., 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- International and Comparative Labor Relations, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Research and Publications, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- 20th Anniversary, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- School Committees, 1961-1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Other (Misc.), 1959-1965 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Weekly Calendars, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Weekly Calendars and Misc. Memos Relating to Weekly Calendars, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)